BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 9) 6178/009
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series XX: Industry Code #71, Arts, Entertainment, and Recreation
  - Theatrical Stage Employees, 1939-1940 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Theatrical Stage Employees, Kansas, 1940 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Theatrical Stage Employees, 1940 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Theatrical Stage Employees, 1937-1940 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Theatrical Stage Employees, 1938-1940 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Theatrical Stage Employees, 1939-1940 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Theatrical Stage Employees, 1937-1940 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Theatrical Stage Employees, 1937-1940 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Theatrical Stage Employees, 1936-1940 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Federal Labor Unions, before 1940, Bowling Alley Pin Setters, 1937-1939 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1940, Entertainment, 1936-1940 (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1942, Arts, Entertainment, and Recreation, 1936-1937 (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - Engineers and Operators, AFL, Theater, 1938-1941 (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - American Federation of Musicians, 1941-1944 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators, 1939-1945 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators, 1938-1941 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Arts and Entertainment, 1942-1944 (Box 129, Folder 27)
- Series XXI: Industry Code #72, Accommodation and Food Services
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, AFL (AZ and CA), 1919-1936 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, AFL (CO, CT, IL, KS, MA, MN, MO, and MT), 1924-1937 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, AFL (NV, NY, OH, OK, OR, and PA), 1926-1936 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, AFL (TX, UT, WA, WV, WI, and WY), 1924-1937 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Federal Workers, CIO, 1945 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    United Cafeteria and Restaurant Workers
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1934-1939 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1936-1939 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1922-1938 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1934-1938 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1935-1938 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1935-1939 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1937-1939 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1935-1939 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1936-1939 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1938-1939 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1939 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1937-1939 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1937-1940 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1937-1940 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1938-1940 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1937-1940 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1939-1940 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1937-1940 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1938-1940 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1939-1940 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1936-1940 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1938-1940 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1937-1940 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1937-1940 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Local Industrial Unions (hotel and restaurant), 1937-1940 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - United Office and Professional Workers, CIO (restaurants), 1938-1940 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Engineers and Operators, AFL, Food Service and Accommodations, 1941-1944 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1939-1946 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Hotels, Cafeterias, and Food Services, 1940-1944 (Box 129, Folder 24)
- Series XXII: Industry Code #81, Other Services (except Public Administration)
  - Journeymen Barbers (CA, CO, CT, and DC), 1924-1933 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Journeymen Barbers (GA, ID, IL, IN, KS, KY, and MA), 1921-1936 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Journeymen Barbers (MI, MN, MS, MO, MT, NE, NH, and NJ), 1921-1937 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Journeymen Barbers (NM, NY, OH, and PA), 1923-1937 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Journeymen Barbers (RI, TN, TX, UT, VA, WA, and WY), 1919-1937 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Federal Locals (cleaners), 1929-1935 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Federal Locals (baths), 1933 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    Russian and Turkish Bath Workers Union
  - Wood, Wire, and Metal Lathers (SC, TN, and TX), 1923-1930 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Wood, Wire, and Metal Lathers (UT and WA), 1903-1935 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Laundry Workers (CA, IL, and MN), 1929-1937 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Laundry Workers (MT, OR, PA, UT, WA, WV, and WI), 1922-1937 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Machinists, general and AZ, 1934-1936 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Machinists, CA and FL, 1932-1936 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Machinists, GA and IL, 1904-1937 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Machinists, IN and IA, 1935 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Machinists, LA and MD, 1927-1935 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Machinists, MN, MO, and MT, 1920-1936 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Machinists, OH and OK, 1932-1937 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Machinists, PA, 1935 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Machinists, TX and WA, 1929-1936 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Machinists, WI, 1932-1936 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Cleaners, Dyers, and Pressers, 1933-1934 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Foreign Documents - Professional Organizations, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    documents from England, Canada, and Scotland
  - Journeymen Barbers, 1925-1938 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Journeymen Barbers, 1928-1939 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Journeymen Barbers, 1921-1939 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Journeymen Barbers, 1937-1938 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Journeymen Barbers, 1930-1938 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Journeymen Barbers, 1939-1940 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Journeymen Barbers, 1937-1940 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Journeymen Barbers, 1935-1940 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Journeymen Barbers, 1937-1940 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Journeymen Barbers, 1934-1940 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Journeymen Barbers, 1935-1940 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Journeymen Barbers, 1937-1940 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Journeymen Barbers, 1937-1940 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Journeymen Barbers, 1939-1940 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Journeymen Barbers, 1937-1940 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Journeymen Barbers, 1939-1940 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Journeymen Barbers, 1937-1940 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Cleaning and Dye House Workers, AFL, 1934-1939 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Cleaning and Dye House Workers, AFL, 1938-1939 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Cleaning and Dye House Workers, AFL, 1937-1939 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Cleaning and Dye House Workers, AFL, 1939-1940 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Cleaning and Dye House Workers, AFL, 1939-1940 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Cleaning and Dye House Workers, AFL, 1935-1940 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Cleaning and Dye House Workers, AFL, 1938-1940 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Cleaning and Dye House Workers, AFL, 1937-1940 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Cleaning and Dye House Workers, AFL, 1938-1940 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Cleaning and Dye House Workers, AFL, 1940 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Cleaning and Dye House Workers, AFL, 1939-1940 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers Association (laundries), 1937-1939 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers Association (laundries), 1937-1939 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers Association (laundries), 1937-1940 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (repair shops), 1937-1941 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Operating Engineers, AFL (laundries), 1939-1940 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Laundry Workers, 1933-1939 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - Laundry Workers, 1935-1938 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - Laundry Workers, 1935-1938 (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - Laundry Workers, 1937-1939 (Box 52, Folder 32)
  - Laundry Workers, 1938-1939 (Box 52, Folder 33)
  - Laundry Workers, 1938-1939 (Box 52, Folder 34)
  - Laundry Workers, 1937-1939 (Box 52, Folder 35)
  - Laundry Workers, 1938-1940 (Box 52, Folder 36)
  - Laundry Workers, 1937-1940 (Box 52, Folder 37)
  - Laundry Workers, 1935-1940 (Box 52, Folder 38)
  - Laundry Workers, 1937-1940 (Box 52, Folder 39)
  - Laundry Workers, 1939-1940 (Box 52, Folder 40)
  - Laundry Workers, 1937-1940 (Box 52, Folder 41)
  - Laundry Workers, 1939-1940 (Box 52, Folder 42)
  - Laundry Workers, 1938-1940 (Box 52, Folder 43)
  - Laundry Workers, 1934-1940 (Box 52, Folder 44)
  - Laundry Workers, 1937-1940 (Box 52, Folder 45)
  - Laundry Workers, 1938-1940 (Box 52, Folder 46)
  - Local Industrial Unions, CIO (barbers), 1937-1939 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Local Industrial Unions, CIO (cemeteries), 1937-1939 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Local Industrial Unions, CIO (laundries), 1937-1940 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Local Industrial Unions, CIO (printing and photo finishing), 1937-1939 (Box 53, Folder 36)
  - Machinists (repair shops), 1936-1940 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - United Office and Professional Workers, CIO (aid and honor societies), 1938-1940 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Federal Labor Unions, before 1940, Cemetery Workers, 1936-1938 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Federal Labor Unions, before 1940, Embalmers, Laundry Services, 1937-1939 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1940, Laundry Services, 1938-1940 (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1942, Object Repair and Maintenance, Laundry Services, Other, 1936-1939 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1944, Death Services, 1943-1944 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Cleaning and Dye House Workers, AFL, 1941-1944 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Engineers and Operators, AFL, Laundry, 1944-1945 (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - Laundry Workers, AFL, 1937-1945 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Private Household Employees (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - St. Louis Funeral Directors, 1941-1942 (Box 128, Folder 16)
  - The Pullman Company (repair), 1944-1945 (Box 129, Folder 13)
  - Cavalry Cemetery Association, 1942 (Box 129, Folder 19)
- Series XXIII: Industry Code #92, Public Administration
  - Reports and Arbitration - Legislative Bodies, 1913-1935 (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - State, County, and Municipal Employees, 1937-1939 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1940, General Information (Box 98, Folder 9)